Loot
[Music]
one
Send a message
[Music] The
waters
[Music]
This issue
you lipstick
looted looted
[Music] The
robbers did it
[Music]
Loot
a sadhu
Candy crush looted-looted
[Music]
Looted
[Music] It has
happened
to
[Music]
Cut it
to Ajay It has
happened to
Ajay
MP3
141 crore jholjhal shadi looted looted
[Music]
Looted
[Music] to
Ajay that
[Music] The
opposition is there do it
[Music]
This issue is
useful
looted
[Music] Turn it on
that I have to get a doctor
looted looted
[Music]
Frustrated looted
[Music] Do it
to Ajay
[Music]
Motu Patlu
[Music] Do it
to Ajay
[Music]
How to make up
looted looted
[Music]
Looted
[Music] Will
go
[Music]
Saadvi ji
a good
[Music] It has happened
Hello hello hello hello everyone Welcome
Today Live Stream Tell me once and the voice will be
clear  Is it working or not there is
a bar located in Jhal, tell me about that and Bittu
give the perfect answer and who is the import first of all
Ashraf tamam come first after that is
Vipin s how to left all are there Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal that
yours have been erased there is a little black going on
tell me once is it okay now or not the
phone number plate is working tell me back
with a little fall I will have to check Jhal Ajay from my side
give feedback of the heroes of Jhal friend
share the ok ok he is very smart he is
pampering too much so it will take some time in those directions
understand that so
let's start today's live
stream and we came a little early so
because of IPL a lot of people were
complaining that they were
not able to watch so I thought why not this is
Jhal so that's why
we have seen this new time today, can the
area go live at this time
or not ok so is this time
good or not tell us let's
start once more index finally this chakli
induction  If we look at the list, we will
first
look at the Nifty as usual. After the replacement of the trend line, Nifty is
quite strong at the level of Z and is
taking support here. If we
look at today's candle and the last three days, we can see a
consolidation-like pattern developing here. So,
in the coming days, we may
see a slight consolidation at this level and
then after Bangladesh, Nifty may
break easily. Okay, so this can happen. The second
pattern is that it consolidates
and then if there is a repeated
reaction in it, it gives a breakdown. Thirdly,
and I think that in
most of the
patterns that are formed like this, when this pattern is
quite common, what happens is that
Nifty is not able to break its three lines, then in such a situation, it does
any torque, that is, it
controls the rate here. Now, the
more Nifty consolidates here, this
trend line will keep blurring like and as
it will come down and then it will break by bouncing from there,
so this also  There are patterns that
can be formed here, so I have presented three patterns
before you, one is by consolidation which suddenly
breaks by forming a big channel, the second is by
consolidating and making a breadth or by continuing to
consolidate so that this trend
line ultimately comes down and when it
is down, it becomes easier to break it, so in
this way you can see this pattern being formed in the net, it will become
clear even today
when the exact soil explains it in this way, it will
also tell a lot that the
pattern is going like this, if we
see educational flight at this level
then the consolidation may increase a little,
but if 1 year 1 is seen going up
then Anisha is seen coming, then the
trend may become clear, let's
move towards the next index,
subscribe to the entire upper line and stay on top,
this pattern because if it
goes below the support of the subscribe union then it
can be seen continuing, the
next
subscribe
button
is breaking the support 06018 public, how should we
look at it carefully, in this
also the policy of our CIT which  It runs away before the rally, so
after the rally we
see a retracement and for the last
four-five years,
we have been seeing similar rallies coming
before the results, sorry, from 45 doctors, like the rich,
but currently
this time what is happening is that it is available before the results
and in China,
we can subscribe from below for
ghee, you can see the subscription for this, a lot of
participation is that
we repeatedly go to a level, the
soil meter and after that there is a
step there, it hangs there, it is
seen in the actual test,
so the bank participation is very good, which is
not visible in the soil and it is
visible well and a
little bit was formed here before breaking the register,
this is a good thing, if such
ghee
breaks 1100
then a rally can be seen in point K, so we have to keep in
mind
what kind
of
appointment
and it was very important that the kind of
quiet patterns that were being formed here, in this
kind of sacred specific pattern was being formed,
treatment is very important in it.  It was and that statement
started but
stay connected from the bottom and there is no doubt
that the
form is continuing from the top that we
liked the channel that after launching it we
saw it coming from the top to the bottom but back to the top so this is also
a solution it is
not looking very good in the end
old old old
so in such a situation if you
get subscribe and
go to the level and then it looks more solid by the way
if you have not bought the board yet then do it
okay so these were
all the index gyms of today we have seen
now let's come to
Twitter about it and there is a picture on Twitter there is
a question and it is taking a lot of time
because of Thursday right now
subscribe
on Gujarat Gas
subscribe subscribe
your buying time so if you
do it for a little short term then it is fine but
if you are buying on line then in my opinion it
performs like this it is more
important this is a very good one
if we look at this animal animal
subscribe
if you have
subscribe to
JSW Energy's gram chart
pattern Dhablu Energy is also very good
Now you should just keep joining a little bit, you should
not subscribe, if you
appoint then in such a situation
entry can be made, the
effect of ghee is being asked for Bala Mines Buy, let's see, the
lawyer prepared by Ahmed Sir,
Klusener has asked,
oh wow sir, the black patterned one can be spread around, there will be
2036, this will have to be put on the box office
and it is possible that if it happens then you will have to agree
subscribe
appointed
that if we look at TVS Motors,
we have been continuously seeing a boil in TVS Motors for the
last few days and you have
written the full name of TVS Motors, which one is left, which one is left on the TV, it does
not happen like this, there are a lot of shares of this name, so
how much did you think,
you
can subscribe to Topper,
subscribe
but no one at all, I should
subscribe from above,
Health Benefits
Quality Limited, so it would have run away on one side, it had
not given much by chance and
what is there now is also by making a pattern  A is
trying to be terrible, so in such a situation,
if we look at the bank's ATM,
Bal Krishna Industries Ltd.,
Ajay, or
Balkrishna Industries, if we look at it,
Balakrishnan Justice Table is visible on
Thursday, but
after that, as soon as we do, the
subscribe button can
go further down, so
ghee can be
appointed in the subscribe, you
can subscribe to what is coming,
so A
Jhal
that Advani Hotels, by no means, the
arm hole will be consolidating,
no problem is visible, it can
definitely be done, when the root of the hole
i.e. Hotels, Tata Motors and Travels will
be on MP, when President SMT can be
bought on HDFC Bank, send help, so
I remember the chart pattern of both, that is
why I told you all without even looking at the chart,
now let's go back to YouTube in the
same way, quickly start your Meghna
and from
here we will start taking the variance, so
someone started putting, all the people who are
continuing are here
and give Bittu's network, what is the
language being used,
if you had asked for the video of the channel portfolio  We will
definitely
make a circle, it will come tomorrow, you will get it,
okay, but the video of the fabric came, so
because of this it got weak, but tomorrow you have four
red chillies,
GPL by entry level, let's see the
oil
and see, the very thing is, ask a little clearly
so that we can also understand, it is
not formed in the body completely,
as can be
seen now, there is no school, ghee can be
kept,
if Hindalco can get good results
then this team can definitely be taken care of,
its mid on shampoo
means
that it will break the level of 564 from this and
Mirza International has 169 target, please,
if you look at Mirza International media, Mirza International, the
targets of Mirza International are almost
cheese, it
is difficult to wait, but if you look at it, then
I think you
should subscribe, let's look at Power Grid
Corporation Limited, Odisha, it happened
on Power Grid,
adding power toe stop is quite good in it,
currently replacing, if you
want to book 50% profit, you can do it very simply, let's
look at
Jhal Titan Company  If we look at it, the retracement
in Titan Company
is still continuing till EM,
I think we should give time, it will come down, it has always been
like a strong support of one and a half policies, if we
look at it then the
100 moving average from here has always been this strong
support, so if it gives up from here also then also the
bank or if it comes down to 2304 then
whatever opportunity will be there, then I
follow the chart, I follow these conditions
and do this, after this it can be seen in detail, let's take a look
that Sir, you would have done live, 732 live has always been
138,
now if we look at the half light, the yellow light is
currently
making EM lower higher higher low pattern,
after this take a bike or if we look at Ashok Leyland
Force Beam,
Ashok Leyland, currently there is a
very good
run-up, so in such a situation, it is coming, there is
no consumption of it at all, there will be
no buy on shampoo at all, so and Vivaan Shah
That the Panchayat has made this sacrifice worth lakhs, that
such a chart pattern is forming, this
Mue Dukhedi is trying to give a reversal, it can be done a few
times, the rest is done
by PM Modi and as it comes out above it,
after that it can be seen for the bike
that it is seen from the east,
Ajay has
his bike at four thousand, it is reducing, there is no
problem, hold it, it will go away,
it always registers with the trend line, so
one minute, if you had
forced it for short term, then I
think if the reaction continues from here,
I will give you one such, from that you have to
exit below the head, the
train line which you were seeing right now, the train line
always touches there,
we can see the retracement coming from there, so
if it is seen coming down from here, then you have to
exit, for now it can be folded, it
breaks the depending, so
this time can be seen going comfortably to your mind level, that is
for short term and it is seen going down, so in
such a situation it can be united.  It is possible that
after this John kept looking at Gopalsar's side,
why does the stock come down as soon as technical support is bought and no, no, it has
not moved till now, sir, then you will look at it properly, you might
not be able to do it, maybe you will
need to learn and let's look at ICICI Lombard
because that does not happen with us, then
I earned profit
relying on technicals only,
serial number of strong which is
in don't train, like number is not at all suitable
for long term, one should not do
banking, if you are performing well then in such a situation you
should be appointed to this post, for
subscription you can see that ghee is
coming below it,
subscribe and
subscribe for it, in the video it is told
that
subscribe
[music]
Bajaj Finserv can also be affected by this serum
and if for short term
then you can get a target of more than 30 in it,
Asian Paints Bank levels are being asked, let's
look at Asian Paints,
if we look at Asian Paints, currently there is a
very good chart
pattern in Asian Paints which is seen tied in or
exactly on CMT  You
can see this for buy, you can vest Paytm
that Arthur is giving reversal of this,
if you are ready to take risk then you
can definitely do Everest, if you already have it, then
if it comes to you then consolidate it
because
on this channel it is mentioned that
if we look at Nestle India than India,
therefore currently there is a pattern in India,
you can definitely do it, therefore, for India Infosys, the
shares were
falling a lot, so if the reverse
subscribe, it will
not be right to subscribe at all,
instead please
subscribe,
after this as you can see
that this result is 10th
result
chart pattern
Raghbir subscribe, by the way,
if you
subscribe to this, your demand is back for Serum, you can take a
bike
on rent, this is being asked of you, let's see the
trend of
Trent Limited, if we look at the
current trend, the real Tanu celebration
pattern is seen forming, the
consolidation pattern, after the consolidation pattern, the
trend is taking support, in
my opinion, very little can be done, so it
felt as if the young man
came and
subscribed  Button products
chart pattern everyone starts a new list and
subscribes to them for reversal and here subscribe and
here
subscribe does
not mean anything, let's look at NSC,
what is the situation in Embassy, ​​if we
look at HTC, the current spread in MSTC,
we see that the retracement John is moving towards the train,
please do it sir, it will
not matter at all, it is asked for B.Ed, let's
look at BSE, if we
look at BSP, if we look at Diya Limited,
BSE Limited is pressing downwards
and has made a lower one, so in this way
I do not think it is very favorable for hair right now, if the retracement
is complete and shows a reversal,
after that, as can be seen for boil, let's look at
Indiamart pressure entry at the
best level, if you
look at MP3, Indiamart, Indiamart is hot, then
Indiamart is currently
forming a reversal pattern, you can get it done in a very
simple way, if you
want to do it, then after this,
for TCS Grasim, there is a son Aryan line
that he  Dividend has been given after a long time,
which share to teach brother, I am on the channel for the first time,
it was new in the market,
Kishore is listed, which one do
you want to tell me, so
let's go, Experience for a Brief Life is
coming, absolutely it can be bought on shampoo, that's why the
flight ran a little in the middle
and after that the correction was quite
good, so the stitching is definitely you
can see it on the ATM for bike,
so after its life, the mixed
laptop that is coming is 50% like Dabir
Vikram, I don't understand anything, if you have any
fear between us, then please send a message, let's
see the anurup,
according to this, if we look at it, then maintenance
currently
yes, the chart pattern is becoming good,
liquidity is a little less, sir, do
not invest too much money in it, it can be done a
little bit on SIM, it has to be
removed, nothing
happened,
Jhal
and Dhani Green Energy, you are asking brother, please
write the full name already, because the
EP latest average of this award
seems a little risky to me  But if
you look at this chart pattern, it looks like a date hanging in the air, so
I wouldn't say for that. If you
take a little time here,
then
subscribing is great, but be a
little careful about it. You should have looked at the position of Daawat. As many
subscribers as you have,
put swelling on whichever pot you subscribe to and
send the link to the Telegram group.
Daawat had a very good chart pattern.
After breaking the train line, when it was
extending upwards, Daawat has gone today. If
you don't have it, then it will
not be good for entry right now. Tata Steel and SAIL are not at
all a problem. Let's
look at Ayush's serial. If I
come, it is a serial
[Sangeet]
Jhal.
Hello, how is the short form of serial?
Tell me the full form because it is not coming from it.
All of it is okay. I am happy with
Indian Oil for u. I am
talking about Indian Oil Corp. Already, if
you have it, then you can see a target of 134 in it.
Now, there is a
variation coming regarding Bharat Dynamics. Let's see, it is Bharat
Dynamics.
If we look at Bharat Dynamics, then
Bharat Dynamics  Currently, it is not an edit
brother, turn on the
Indian dynamics, currently EM is already
very much filled, I will
tell you all clearly what is the
reaction, if you want to know then why is
this talk tick tok, yes or no, tell me quickly, if you
want to know what is the reason,
first of all it is certain that as soon as the
deal is received in India, the related equipment has been
installed on them, if they are
not able to do it, if they need it
then they will have to talk to the Indian partner, the partner
Indian company,
secondly, there can be a matter regarding the manufacturing of the product in India in the manufacturing of Modi and in
that,
grh grh k,
nothing can be done about this mask, it is so
hot, I cannot sit in the heat, I was
sitting till now, I will show you,
you would sit in the heat by switching off the fan
and today it is very much, let us
look at AIIMS hospital,
TMC hospital,
Ajay, or
Cancer hospital, if we look at the chart pattern, then
this downtrend is quite strong  It will
not remain in it at all, if it is there then
open it, but for the press bike, I will
not say this from my side, sir, the printout is
not clear, the
price chart is not clear, please give me that at
this place, all this is
completely clear on my side,
this is completely clear on my side, the chart
is there,
wait for a minute
because perhaps it is not visible clearly to you, if it is
not visible clearly to you, then
yes, it is Baby Capital 6206,
AB Chapter Aditya Birla Capital, ruined
companies, Sarovar Dam companies, I think
fold it, I am not able to understand the
chart pattern,
subscribe
and town more 06018
Tata Consumer Program, if
you see the chart pattern then what is there in Tata Consumer Products, currently, on
one side, one
should wait for youth,
after that, the young
generation will
not subscribe because
in my opinion, subscribing to any such
level
here is
absolutely not possible, there will be a
network problem from the room's side, that is why
they are not able to see it,
Electra  350 or I take support
Ajay
also in shells but you have support left that
white you have not covered the head has
broken the support and it does
not seem to be calling much either I do not
subscribe from
above
someone
in the middle
brought about the subscribe company
yes there was a lot of
talk
when the rally of this sector had started
and it was going on these talks about tractors latest
trend
subscribe if you
subscribe
then it will
not be good for too much
I had already told you a while ago that if
you talk about subscribing against the youth then it is formed like this
it is formed around
158 so how do you place f-18 then
how does it form 3-4 percent in such a situation it can definitely be done
absolutely you can do it it is
almost
certain
that this level of 171 will be the target
and if it goes above it then in such a situation it can
definitely be seen to press further
let's see first my idea towards next use for 2 minutes is
that
and I have turned on
one percent charge
We will start taking the variation again. I had put it
on charge. I
forgot to switch on the Prabhu, due to this the
torch has gone off. What has happened is that JK
Tyres shoulder exit poll. If we
look at the JK Tyre retired employee pattern, then
JK Tyre currently has a profit booking
level. If we look at it, then this which
came from the subscribe, but subscribe from above.
If you see this, then let's take the
shoulder of the energy, that
if we look at Sadhna Energy Sarda Energy, it was currently on
in the diner, it is
completely folded. I am not seeing any chances
of gender from anywhere above the chart pattern, okay you
can fold it. You can subscribe to cosmos100 cosmos100 appointed at the office.
Now it is visible that the arrest is going to be completed very
soon.
And how many people are here for the first time,
how many people have
subscribed?  As many people can be seen
subscribing,
thankfully for Team India, all the
new topics that were listed in the last few days,
after that, I saw
that the
don trend was visible
in all the spots, now a reversal pattern is
visible, a chart pattern like PT
was forming, but if the dam was extended to one side, then in this way
I don't stay with Lord Vishnu for long like
Aamir Khan, let's subscribe a little and
turn from 06, it has happened
at 206, you have filed a bank complaint,
why do you have to completely fold sir,
look at this, what a lovely chart pattern is this, a
festival chart pattern is forming, it might
seem medium to you, but you
can easily go into the chart that
in war,
and after this, what is coming for me regarding Awadh Sugar, you will
definitely be able to do it, take a look at the chart of 732 once,
Singh ji had said that today there was a little sweetness in the sugar stock, these are his
words, I have mentioned here during one and
a half Awadh Sugar,
Awadh Sugar is a very good chart pattern,
Babu, fold it and if you want to talk then it can
also be done bye, okay, let's
look at its India, we will
see the chart pattern of India,
India  You are current
and tell me,
hey brother, who has asked a lot,
when do you go live? The time is during the day,
live like at 8:00 in the morning and
definitely at 7:30 in the evening. We did
n't subscribe a little early, so because of that we
watched it a little early, let's watch
Dr. Reddy's, first
thank them,
skip the Indians, thank you two months
ago, everyone, escape the India one,
click on it, let me give
you the track, I'm
distracted by the Indian PM,
okay, we want to talk about the PM,
if we think about uniting India by leaving this printed movie unclaimed,
chart
patterns, lots of love, you need to
subscribe.
Secondly, if you ca
n't subscribe, I'm not going to subscribe to the
B.Sc. Colleges pattern right now. Country by,
see this, Rohit, Shivale
Bhai had asked about India, that's why
he is writing back, it can be done,
absolutely it can be done,
everyone, it's going to thank you. Let's
look at the Apple pressure entry and targets. What happened was that
our monitors were taking credit.  It
happened, wash it with shampoo, very good
chart pattern did
not subscribe,
catch
Madrasan Sumi, one,
that Madrasan Sumi is completely folded, it is fine, I will tell
you how you can tell, if you have
not seen your chart then it is
giving reversal adding to the beauty of the day, there is no problem, it is
completely folded, there
will be no problem
in Madrasan Sumi,
this is being asked on Pilani Investment, you should have seen it, is
Pilani Investment, if you
see Pilani Investment, then it is
not currently on Pilani Investment, sir, if you have it then it will
not be in the holder press, if
not subscribed then
I
also do not do it, so the
next one is that the tower was
always on top,
if he had
taken it in this video, it would have happened, if he had
not subscribed,
sir, it is not taking the verification today, your luck will
not be good, what should we do, just
look at Goa Carbon, friend,
what will we get, you should
turn off the heat sitting here so that you keep
sitting and getting troubled in the heat
and you are saying that war does not happen like this
and aunt's descendant is more  I felt like avoiding it, it might not have
come yet, it presses, it starts
forming your pattern, so in such a situation, it will be
seen for the bike, you are being
asked this, it was written at one time
that Padhani was a gas-based company, but
current should be taken so that it is falling more, that
detail has become very high, the company is
trying to give a reversal, but many
times they have tried to give a pack reversal,
so if you want to do it, then you should not do it completely,
if this festival develops a chart pattern, you have increased the
position from the top, Dr. Reddy's, till then you will have to
fold,
shares 0
Dr. Reddy's
Labs, there is no problem, if the doctor has said it, then
definitely
fold it with patience, if you have taken it for short term, then
you would not have taken it, if you have taken Dr. Reddy's, then you have done
5,000, then it will
not be for short term only, because
subscribe, a
pattern like inverted shoulder can be
kept by folding, you will have to keep it till then,
I can tell you and you should definitely subscribe to TVS Motors, a
fall below that was seen, so do
not make it a loophole and slap  If I start giving it, it must be
for Firoz Bhai, it must be for special purpose
or if you have it right now, then it can be kept
folded. Renuka
Sugars is asking for celery.
Renuka Sugar, Mr. Renuka Sugar, how many people are there
who are watching this film for the first time,
hashtag 1like, all the people who are watching for the
first time, that Renuka Sugar will not be made from the problem at
all,
how can you ask for fresh peas after running away from thirteen percent,
I do not understand brother,
but such people ask, who
see the regular reaction, then one thing that watching your session must
mean is that you just
ask your questions and leave, you do
not learn anything, or you are just busy in copy-paste, copy-
paste, in which you are
not able to do anything, then you do anything in it, then
I think you are going wrong,
like you, there should be knowledge in it, not asking for stocks, so let's survive
on the national minimum,
subscribe to the channel, subscribe to my channel,
then I saw a slight decline
and yes the channel
cannot be subscribed,
that war  I will not do
Vishal Agarwal
subscribe so
I Sandeep Verma Sir, this is the first time I am being
asked about Prequel as well, if we
look at Prequel then of course I am seeing a
slight retracement after Anil Rana, so
from there this time it has been seen that
if we look at the chart pattern of the call then it is a
hydrate chart pattern, if
you take it on PM then in such a situation the
formation of approximately 6% in the pimple can be done
here, the
pattern comes and it comes very quickly,
so I have to exit, don't
wait too much,
Chambal Fertilizer but 485 please suggest
Chambal Fertilizer, there is no problem, the
fertilizer is seen performing from the stop
subscribe, it is seen
that the question is coming about Shalimar Paints,
I think if you want to go into the market then like
Indian Mujahideen then ice will freeze
Shalimar etc. there is no
point in going into the stop with low market share, the chart pattern is also a
drama  Why is it not visible, the
pattern like People Top Ten is being formed in it, it will
not remain at all, let's look at B-1 B-2
B-3
and see the order chart pattern of the bell, then the
color in the middle must have been well formed, that it can be done at
all, there is no
problem, that it can be folded at all,
now look at the oil, this deal
news, no one can tell you in which it can be said, as
I told you a while ago,
first of all, that
news on the product and between today
and
India,
regarding some product manufacturing,
and if the government government
subscribes,
all these staff appointed,
when the
school
could not tell the subscription, that of
war, Akshay was not registered, okay, do not
use the call word, that war is not right, from
there onwards, the
subscription takes so much time,
if you are seen taking so much time, then our
team is there to see you,
which word has happened, do not use it,
please, that is why for that, we are not all registered,
so we have appointed anyone,
you are seeing the chart, we are analyzing it, we are doing it
accordingly, stop panel chart  Which one is being
made, ghee is made like this, chaat is made of this,
okay, so if you subscribe,
if
you do
not want to subscribe, no such chart pattern is formed,
that is why it should go
up a little, you
can start doing it above this, you
give it completely traditional, do not give calls,
ICICI Prudential is being asked for tea,
I laughed, if you look at Prudential then the addition will
not be for the long term, if you want to
see a company in this sector in the long term, then there are
two companies, okay, so
his life and the other one is SBI Life, SBI
Life probably made a very big candle today,
Meena, ICICI Prudential is
not right as per the orders, so in such a situation I will avoid it,
Sunil sir, sorry, no, I just want to avoid it because there are
many things,
if it gets completed, there can be a
problem, you can divide the price of Dish TV, you should have
seen Dish
TV, when the channel became so big, Aaj Tak, there was no
tension, does it happen that
as the channel grows,
some people like the channel,
some people do not like the channel, like
all of you  The 194 people sitting here are
liking the channel but there are
some people whose queries would have been
written on this, then if they would have gone and complained then
that legal a little bit in it,
God, that is why Uppal word should not be used,
ah as far as Dish TV is concerned, avoid it,
it goes down in a very good chart pattern, so
you may get launched, so in
such a situation, if you can watch it for subscription here,
I had told you, but even today it is available,
what is it by Akbar, sir, ah,
if we look at Bank of Baroda, I am in Bank of Baroda,
oh how much will you get currently, I made a
mistake, sir, while running I put it in the city,
you do not have to do this, you do not have to do this, and the
rich people should
always watch it and Rishu,
why do we always say this, ah, at all the
detergent continues, go through
this,
Radio City, please, everyone is being asked for a like,
probably for the first time, oh
Swami Sir, probably this is the first time,
oh my god, why like  If you are not liking it,
friends, you guys should turn it
on,
why are you not liking it,
how many people are there who have not liked it yet, then
quickly like it, you can see Radio
City till then, get the music, see what you think, the chart will
tell you
what to do,
I don't think we need to tell you anything,
in this chart, which you
regularly see, what should be done, in such a situation, I had
not booked profit of 1000 before this parma, but it was
not going above 120,
well, it could be on
your side,
okay, I laugh when someone
asks that in so many days, it could
go up to this much,
sir, if the market was running by editing on time,
it is not a rain that it will come
in two-four days, the reversal
chart can go up a little,
maximum 12138
subscribers, very good, from home, instead of
subscribing to a kind of yagya,
subscribe completely, you enjoy it,
hey friend,
we are looking for that, I will
also give you a target,
if you see Rafi, it was
jhala, so
see what idea is forming, sir  I am
showing the chart of what happened, from here Bigg
Boss takes back serum also, but bikers will be the
first target, it will be made thirteen, there are
more chances of launch in
Jhalawar or not, that does not depend on me,
okay, so you can fine-tune the idea with your wrist, I have
told the SMS partner and the fairy is coming regarding power,
probably there are a lot of new people, all the
new people who come, friend, these kind of companies are
not bike companies, avoid that
kind of company which
we look at lightly,
welcome love welcome left, it is a
company with good fundamentals, when I
started studying fundamentals, when I had a
complaint in the beginning, then when I
looked at the fundamentals of this company, you said that it is
related to the pharma sector, then it would
not be right to talk in such a situation, there is nothing special as far as chart pattern is concerned,
and tell me,
sir, you control your anger so much, it has become a
habit now, when you
look at NMDC short term target, do you get
angry because I know this thing,
why do you get angry, tell me, this is a useless
statement to you  My voice if you
don't see your energy, you can be a little tired,
subscribe if you already have it,
prank you sir, you are good,
a reminder, reminder level is being asked, it happened
yesterday also, the minister told me in yesterday's video, the
commentary which will be
seen on TV in a little decline, so I would
say that waiting for Bigg Boss
appointment, as it gives, then it can be seen in it, if
we see this person, if we
want to talk about the CM in HDFC, then
you will have to wait till later, as it is tied,
after that it will be seen completely, once the
Pune robbers have
subscribed to them, the
Pune wala Poonawala has gone up tremendously, do it, on top of that there is
selling pressure also,
so in such a situation it will not be right to talk
or
Jethalal is getting a return of Rs 5400 in Mirza International
and should I share it or make a
profit,
if you are getting a 10 percent return
from gas in Mirza International, I
would say that ok follow, right now there will be no one
that the war
repeats,
then  The
appointments are
not done completely, I have
no problem with them,
I don't have any problem with any stock, the
problem is that retail
investors lose their hard earned money due to their stupidity,
why not, where is stupid, when
you set a response for a new person, then
that person never gets it straight,
if someone is asking me for an idea, he
is new to the market or he has not learned, that is why he is
asking, then if we make fun of him, then
he will not get it, that poor fellow will
not ask out of fear, the next
time I get angry because
retail investors repeat the same mistake, what
we saw happening in Yes Bank,
we saw it happening in the idea,
retail investors subscribe in every stock with long term trend, even
after that if retail
investors are making
mistakes again and again, then
I think that
if you will waste your hard earned money like this
and we will talk  I am
thinking that wealth building should be weight,
we should earn money, our long-term
goal is that the goal should be
good, so you will eat good food only then you will get a good body,
whatever you have will remain when you eat good food, then
when will your portfolio be good
or will
your portfolio be good only if
you buy good stocks, that is why it happened
and you should always buy well,
okay, if there are too many photos etc. then
learn to control it a little, I know
that the form will not be controlled in one day,
it will not be controlled at all in one day, it will take
time, but you can
try, from the last time I had a problem,
I learned that oh
no brother, you can try to control it a little,
no one is perfect, Jain
Amit, no one is perfect, but from yesterday to
today and the day after tomorrow, you can become even better, whether it is
in technical analysis
or in the market or in your life,
so think like this a little, if you
think like that then in the long run I want
that those of you who are  You both are
giving one and a half hour of yours for us,
so we too should not be able to give something to you in your life,
you just saw, we
asked and told you some top choices which
you made in profit, some time has passed, I feel
that if we run this channel for the
next five years, then all of you should
subscribe to me, that is when I started
and today
I want such people, all those
businessmen,
now the anger is because
even after telling all this,
if it is not happening
or if your money or you
know anywhere, what can I do,
you people join here, you
feel that something bad should
not happen to anyone, let's see, let's
move in that direction, so
if you have a chart pattern, it can be done
for both of you, that 108, it was folded, to
subscribe, make the payment here, the
link is in the description and if you have it, then it is a
little far away here,
I would also like you to
see us in 5 years, when we meet up after 5 years,
all those people who have big portfolios  If the
people of India bring big portfolios, it will be a
good thing, it will be fun, we will feel
that we have done something in Pakistan, I am not at all going to create
thousands of YouTube channels, I am not at all
lucky to have done this, I am
not getting much, then I get angry, there is
loss in the market, that is what happens, do it to
Ajay, I have
seen the hot chart pattern of Redington India,
what is there in Redington India is becoming a very good chart
pattern, if you want to take care of the CM, you
can fine-tune Redington India, whatever will be your target, it will be
177, Chambal Fertilizer fee has
come to profit booking on Chambal Fertilizers side,
because now
I do not think that you will get an opportunity for this bike, it has
not reached at all, it has reached the
level of profit booking, all
time interest litigation, so our target of
4865, that does not matter now,
if we look at the past, currently there is consolidation going on in Cipla, a
little bit of 30% of the remaining districts, and
when the train caught, after that it happened
more times  You can go sir the pot whose
live session
is expensive the
regular team probably your net will
not have any subscription
you can talk to your internet provider from this side also
if they change it you can
see the tech bike range the tech bike range the tech bike
jhala ok you are
listening to the interview inside you don't have to do it at all
you must have heard there is an interview on this
subscribe at all
it is
a place on the
left side
my name is written in
benefit tracking in the
register of
that bill we have banked our voice you
all will remember that it must have been 15 days since you
last did this I already
keep it fierce it is taking the resistance of the trend line in
my opinion there is no resistance of the trend line like
this is not the first target
for profit booking you can do profit booking for
Tata Motors
option no let's not talk about it
subscribe
subscribe so at
this time give us something for that then Ajay so let's
see and supervisor can be done come to
you regardless of that
it is melted that
limited means of on media  And if you
look at the printed media, whatever you have done, then if
you have already done it, then do it,
please do it, the rest will not be for like right now,
Wipro
7570 was 21, this should be folded,
you can see a little race happening,
so you can subscribe a little, I am
not able to find a technical analyst, share some idea
and that will happen
and keep
watching, the
more people
subscribe, it is
not a matter of understanding, it is
more a matter
of practice than understanding, so the more
you practice in technical analysis, the more you will get
fitted here, it was done
regarding Larsen & Toubro,
if you look at Larsen & Toubro, the
rickshaw from below is
seen to be tracing from above, but there is
no such problem in the chart, so it can
definitely be folded, Larsen &
Toubro can be added to Tata Motors,
yes, yes, you are asking by changing the question, it is good,
Tata Motors midnight can be added a
little,
you should
subscribe for a short time, as
many people as possible
from the side for the first time.  If it's from the village,
let's keep liking. We're building towards India,
so all the people who are there, keep liking.
Now, be smart and avoid talking at this level.
Please, it's not appropriate to talk about it at this level. It's being
asked for painter level.
Hello friends, if you look at the page, there's a
current legend double stone pattern in the Prince Pipe.
Melt a little bit of this water, just a little bit of sugar, and positions will be created. Stay away from home. And when it
falls, you get 10 lakh
subscribers.
Look at this, a market fall or market price is something that
happens once in 10 years, so I'll
wait for it. All of you are already
subscribed.
If someone asks you,
subscribe,
grh grh k, what do you
think is the best time to limit your investment? Till then,
look at the solar industry.
What do you think would be the best time to invest in it?
Tell me,
brother, your
Bitcoin, our portfolio speed, it has
n't been affected. It wo
n't happen if the color comes on duty. And
if you have time, it can be
folded, absolutely
no problem. Add Infosys Tata once the
replacement is complete.  Give it
after that which can be seen for a bike,
best book for technical analysts,
nothing will happen on this issue, you have to pick up any book
of Ravi Patel, I
gave so much advertisement, that guy
is also not ready to give me money
and then I told him that brother, give it to me, you are doing so much
attachment on the channel, I am joking,
okay, it is
best to invest in Ravi Patel and it is
best to subscribe
if you are from the market,
then slowly slowly  You can keep investing,
okay, but you should start from today
because unless you see this,
until you
invest in the market, you do
n't follow the market. Many people think that until you don't have a
little money, you do
n't have money, that is,
you don't have any
interest in the market, you should
build a position slowly, net,
yes, once the retracement is complete,
Abhijeet, and after that, you can do it very minutely, yes, at
this point, you
can also read that, absolutely anyone can buy it, you don't have to
read it, you just have to
subscribe to the chart pattern,
it is the time when you
can give a target of 130 to
Arthur Ashe
Ajay, which
Manipuram is 130, why did the financier give it,
why, what happened, why is it not loading, turn it on, the
chart is not loading, everything is behind,
speech by, today a good result has come, go to its
chart, TCS is seen falling,
currently, the chart is not loading at the current levels.
And I
needed a minute, I thought
wait a minute, a little chart, if it was
not working then
fold these IS, sir, there was no problem,
write them together, it will go up a little in a line, it will go
up and down, so
you will have to handle it, if you
cannot understand the quality then
stay away from the market, then go to the store,
it is not of any quality at all,
okay, go there, if
you are not able to handle even 2% of the quality then you
should go, you
mean you will go crazy, then
okay, there is no need to explain the situation, it is
taking a lot of time, I don't know, look for the
biggest companies, I will give you
0A class, invest in it, make 10,000 and
see,
Ajay, let's
look at TCS,
Ajay,
Ajay, it has been
very good this year, if yes, then a
little bit of banking can be done today itself,
overall IT systems and a
little bit is visible in it, so you
can go in such a way that when the
reversal, after that you can make it here, then
subscribe completely, what has
happened is that  You are asking for a shot in Spain
because it was at 140, as far as it is concerned, it can
give a good target of 130, if it gives a reversal from here, it can
go up to 146, so
in such a situation, there is no point here, it can be
folded, the main in the
rings festival asked, the
team has established a minimum balance system, show me the
reddy of 2018, you show me the
ad, brother add a
main, this amazing
series pattern has been formed inside, it is visible,
now after this, see here, this can be
seen for the festival, there
is an appeal in subscribing to it and we have already subscribed,
if you want to talk, you
can definitely do it, the target which will be
543, it will come out above that, it can
definitely be seen for the next target, we are
considering the option of a hotel, let's see, put and take out, put and take out, as far as it is
concerned, it is
in reducing the nickel,
avoid it, it is becoming exactly like this,
we have given a little reversal here
and it will happen because it is not right on orders, so in such a situation,
use it in such a way
that I am not tomorrow  If we
look at the inner wear is program, then the energy
brings reversal is taking place in a proper manner,
not at all a little bit of money,
after that as can be done,
please take a look,
so if we look at those products Tarzan products, then a
reversal chart pattern was formed in Tarzan product,
after that a rally was seen, today
this does not do all right, so in such a situation, we can
see there is a
subscribe entry
and there is number 01, so let's see, there was
a
reminder to the number, Swiss and moving towards the ending, let's
move towards India, long avoid,
avoid, there will be no such thing in it, all the
people are
quickly going towards themselves and let's take,
Tata Power, Tata Wasim will be taken care of, all the
major entries will be there,
regarding JP Power, my report is coming, there is a
little bit of fennel on BJP,
friends, this is the topic, so in such a case, the report in
which there will be Dada, if
my channel is
not getting subscribed, then there is
no need to worry, you have to
subscribe, so
come here, we will quickly tell you a
little bit about it, as I told you earlier, it happened and
If he speaks too loudly, then
perhaps the situation could have become old, so in
such a situation, I have tried to talk slowly
with my energy, which could
not be an option today, let me tell all the new people who have come
that our station which is at
1:30 in the afternoon and 7:30 in the evening, do
not forget to join the organization of both, so all the people who are new, you can get a
discount from one of our committees, so if
you know how to use this point, then definitely
use the biscuit,
join our cord committee so that the
old members who have already
taken our experience,
if you have come to know about how the channel is and
if you want to connect with us more,
want to talk to us more personally, then in
such a situation you can join the book club,
here we put in front of you the option to subscribe
and investment
on subscription, the decision is
yours, whether you invest in it or not,
you can join that too,
in the link description I will say the mode of Bigg
Boss here, click on it  Let me
tell you the thing about subscription that we
are subscribed, do
not forget to follow the English subscribe, it has to be
folded like this, do
not forget to follow that and you must have joined on Telegram till now,
what are you talking about, you have
not joined yet, hey brother, go and
join on Telegram first so that
you will keep getting updates of the station, I will meet you like this
in the next session, till then say
bye-bye
[Music]